Guide to the Edwin Richard Weinerman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Consultations, Projects, and Professional Assignments, 1943-1970; Series II; 12 linear feet (26 boxes, 1 carton)
  - Family Health Record Study
    - record books for Family Health Study, undated (Box 31, Folder 111)
    - figures and graphs, undated (Box 31, Folder 112)
    - comment on the Family Health Record Study, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 113)
  - Multiphasic Health Tests
    - Correspondence:
      - Breslow, Lester (2), 1950 (Box 31, Folder 114)
      - Dodd, J. M. (1), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 114)
      - Hollinger, Nell (2), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 114)
      - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (2), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 115)
      - Karas, Felix C. (1), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 115)
      - Mac Pherson, Gwen (1), 1952 (Box 31, Folder 115)
      - Merrill, Malcolm H. (1), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 116)
      - Milmore, B. K. (1), 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 116)
      - The Permanente Foundation (1), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 116)
      - Sage, E. C. (1), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 117)
      - Scherer, S. N. (1), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 117)
      - Silberstein, Irwin W. (1), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 117)
      - Waybur, Anne (1), 1952 (Box 31, Folder 117)
      - minutes of meetings on multiphasic health testing, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 118)
      - memoranda and notes on procedures for multiphasic testing, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 119)
      - medical questionnaires (Box 31, Folder 120)
      - letters sent to participants in multiphasic testing (Box 31, Folder 121)
      - ILWU promotional material for multiphasic testing (Box 31, Folder 122)
      - photographs of multiphasic testing (Box 31, Folder 123)
      - magazine and newspaper clippings on multiphasic testing (Box 31, Folder 124)
      - "Multiphasic Screening of Long shoremen with Organized Medical Follow-up" by E. R. Weinerman et al, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 125)
      - "Non-Response to Medical Follow-up in a Multiphasic Screening Program" by M. Shain (Box 31, Folder 126)
      - misc. health care pamphlets (Box 31, Folder 127)
      - misc. (Box 31, Folder 128)
  - San Francisco Labor Council Survey
    - Correspondence:
      - San Francisco Labor Council (4), 1952 (Box 32, Folder 129)
      - San Francisco Medical Society (1), n. d. (Box 32, Folder 129)
      - "The San Francisco Labor Health Survey" (draft of Labor Plans for Health ), 1952 (Box 32, Folder 130)
      - Labor Plans for Health by E. R. Weinerman, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 131)
      - Labor Plans for Health (introduction and conclusions), 1952 (Box 32, Folder 132)
      - Labor Plans for Health (conclusions), 1952 (Box 32, Folder 133)
      - Labor Plans for Health (summary of findings and recommendations), 1952 (Box 32, Folder 134)
      - background material, notes, and tables for Labor Plans for Health (Box 32, Folder 135)
      - grant proposals for a labor health center, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 136)
      - memoranda and minutes re: proposed labor health center, 1952, undated (Box 32, Folder 137)
      - notes and financial materials re: proposed labor health center, 1952, undated (Box 32, Folder 138)
      - San Francisco Labor Council Official Bulletin, 1951-1954 (Box 32, Folder 139)
      - San Francisco Labor (newspaper of the San Francisco Labor Council), 1952, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 140)
      - magazine articles re: labor health survey, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 141)
      - newspaper articles and clippings re: labor health surrey (Box 32, Folder 142)
      - misc. brochures (Box 32, Folder 143)
  - The President's Commission on the Health Needs of the Nation
    - agendas and background material, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 144)
    - summaries of panel discussions, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 145)
    - "General Practice" (report for use of Commission), 1952 (Box 33, Folder 146)
    - "Group Practice in the United States" (report for the use of the Commission), 1952 (Box 33, Folder 147)
    - "Organization for Health Services" (charts and tables for the use of the Commission), 1952 (Box 33, Folder 148)
  - Herrick Memorial Hospital Clinics
    - reports on professional consultation and referral, 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 149)
    - notes, schedules, and statistics re: Herrick Memorial Hospital Clinics, 1958-1961, undated (Box 33, Folder 150)
    - papers re: intensive care unit, 1959-1961, undated (Box 33, Folder 151)
    - application for research grant: "Health Maintenance for the Aging in a Hospital Setting", 1958 (Box 33, Folder 152)
    - application for research grant (early drafts and preparatory material) (Box 33, Folder 153)
    - notes for seminars in medical socio-economics, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 154)
    - by-laws of the medical staff of Herrick Memorial Hospital, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 155)
    - bulletins and pamphlets (Box 33, Folder 156)
  - Berkeley Health Plans
    - memoranda, notes, and plans re: proposed Berkeley health plan, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 157)
    - memoranda, notes, and plans re: proposed Berkeley health plan, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 158)
    - memoranda, notes, and plans re: proposed Berkeley health plan, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 159)
  - United Mine Workers of America Welfare and Retirement Fund Survey of Clinics
    - Correspondence:
      - Centerville Clinic (4), 1962 (Box 34, Folder 160)
      - Falk, Leslie Alan (32), 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 160)
      - Ferrier, Thomas A. (3), 1959 (Box 34, Folder 161)
      - Perunko, Polly A. (2), 1960 (Box 34, Folder 161)
      - outline and plans for survey of UMWA clinics, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 162)
      - "Report of a Survey of the Group Medical Clinics Serving Beneficiaries of the UMW Welfare and Retirement Fund in the Pittsburgh Area" by E. R. Weinerman, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 163)
      - background material and notes on Centerville clinic (Box 34, Folder 164)
      - background material and notes on Russellton clinic (Box 34, Folder 165)
      - background material and notes on Bellaire clinic (Box 34, Folder 166)
      - memoranda and papers re: Bellaire clinic and denial of hospital privileges, 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 167)
      - background material and notes re: 1962 re-evaluation of Centerville clinic (Box 34, Folder 168)
    - background material and notes re: 1962 re-evaluation of Centerville clinic (Box 34, Folder 169)
    - outline and report of 1962 re-evaluation of Centerville clinic (Box 34, Folder 170)
  - Miners Memorial Hospital Association Survey of Hospitals
    - Correspondence:
      - Barnes, Asa (9), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 171)
      - Brooke, Dean Francis (6), 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 171)
      - Daniels, Henry C. (7), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 172)
      - Draper, Warren Fales, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 172)
      - Esson, William B. (5), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 173)
      - Falk, Leslie Alan (6), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 173)
      - Greeley, David McLean (2), 1961 (Box 34, Folder 173)
      - Kistin, Albert D. (5), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 174)
      - Knutti, Sarah H. (3), 1961 (Box 34, Folder 174)
      - Meade, Gordon Montgomery (4), 1961 (Box 34, Folder 174)
      - Newdorp, John (19), 1960 (Box 34, Folder 175)
      - Newdorp, John (17), 1961 (Box 34, Folder 176)
      - Rannels, Herman W. (3), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 177)
      - Riheldaffer, William Howard (10), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 177)
      - Robinson, A. H. (1), 1960 (Box 34, Folder 178)
      - Wilder, Theodore S. (6), 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 178)
      - Winebrenner, John D. (8), 1960-1962 (Box 34, Folder 178)
      - outline and notes (Box 35, Folder 179)
      - plan and evaluation criteria for MMHA survey (Box 35, Folder 180)
      - "Report of a Survey of the Miners Memorial Hospital Association" by E. R. Weinerman, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 181)
      - "Report of a Survey of the Miners Memorial Hospital Association" by E. R. Weinerman, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 182)
      - general information on UMWA Welfare and Retirement Fund and MMHA Hospitals (Box 35, Folder 183)
      - general information on MMHA Hospitals (Box 35, Folder 184)
      - data on MMHA physicians (Box 35, Folder 185)
      - financial statements, etc. (Box 35, Folder 186)
      - statistical reports (Box 35, Folder 187)
      - background material and notes on Beckley Area Medical Office (Box 35, Folder 188)
    - background material and notes on Charleston Area Medical Office (Box 35, Folder 189)
    - background material and notes on Knoxville Area Medical Office (Box 35, Folder 190)
    - background material and notes on Louisville Area Medical Office (Box 35, Folder 191)
    - background material and notes on Beckley Memorial Hospital (Box 35, Folder 192)
    - background material and notes on Harlan Memorial Hospital (Box 35, Folder 193)
    - background material and notes on Man Memorial Hospital (Box 35, Folder 194)
    - background material and notes on Pikeville Memorial Hospital (Box 35, Folder 195)
    - background material and notes on Williamson Memorial Hospital (Box 35, Folder 196)
    - background material and notes on Wise Memorial Hospital (Box 35, Folder 197)
    - articles re: Miners Memorial Hospital Association (Box 36, Folder 198)
    - pamphlets re: Miners Memorial Hospital Association (Box 36, Folder 199)
    - misc. (Box 36, Folder 200)
  - Group Health Association
    - background material and notes (Box 36, Folder 201)
    - "Report of a Survey of Group Health Association" by E. R. Weinerman, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 202)
  - Community Health Association, Santa Rosa
    - Correspondence:
      - Community Health Association (5), 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 203)
      - Grami, William (11), 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 204)
      - Hines, Leonard W. (13), 1961-1963 (Box 36, Folder 204)
      - Neyhart and Grodin (2), 1961 (Box 36, Folder 205)
      - Yedidia, Avram (1), 1962 (Box 36, Folder 206)
      - memoranda and notes re: founding of Community Health Association, 1961-1962, undated (Box 36, Folder 207)
      - agreements and by-laws, 1959, undated (Box 36, Folder 208)
      - "Standards for Control of Quality of Medical Care" (draft outline) by E. R. Weinerman, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 209)
      - newspaper clippings and pamphlets (Box 36, Folder 210)
  - United Automobile Workers and American Motors Corporation
    - Correspondence:
      - American Motors Corp. (3), 1961 (Box 37, Folder 211)
      - Cohen, Martin (2), 1961 (Box 37, Folder 211)
      - Goldstein, David N. (1), 1961 (Box 37, Folder 212)
      - Yedidia, Avram (4), 1961 (Box 37, Folder 212)
      - "Report of a Preliminary Survey of Medical Care Plans…" by E. R. Weinerman and A. Yedidia, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 213)
      - notes and outline (Box 37, Folder 214)
  - Community Health Foundation, Cleveland
    - Correspondence:
      - Altman, Isidore (16), 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 215)
      - Ballard, Barbara (2), 1965 (Box 37, Folder 215)
      - Bond, Douglas D. (1), 1962 (Box 37, Folder 215)
      - Brewster, Agnes W. (7), 1961-1965 (Box 37, Folder 215)
      - Community Health Foundation (4), 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 216)
      - Copperman, Michael (14), 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 216)
      - Davis, Burnet (1), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 217)
      - Davis, Walter L. (1), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 217)
      - Dearing, W. Palmer (1), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 217)
      - Dingle, John (1), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 217)
      - Ebert, Robert Higgins (2), 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 218)
      - Finley, Joanne E. (29), 1963-1965 (Box 37, Folder 218)
      - Gonerman, Alice (4), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 219)
      - Greenlick, Merwyn R. (1), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 219)
      - Henderson, Marie B. (1), 1966 (Box 37, Folder 219)
      - Householder, Lucy (3), 1962, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 219)
      - Howley, Lee (3), 1966, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 220)
      - Little, Robert A. (1), 1962 (Box 37, Folder 220)
      - Mac Leod, Gordon K. (1), 1967 (Box 37, Folder 220)
      - Mallett, David L. (2), 1967 (Box 37, Folder 220)
      - Moss, Edwyne (12), 1961-1963 (Box 37, Folder 220)
      - Ort, Robert S. (4), 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 221)
      - Oseasohn, Robert (2), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 222)
      - Paley, Warren (7), 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 222)
      - Pearson, David A. (3), 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 222)
      - Pearson, John C. (1), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 222)
      - Rammelkampf, Charles (2), 1962, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 223)
      - Saward, Ernest W. (1), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 223)
      - Shapiro, Sam (4), 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 223)
      - Sloss, John H. (15), 1960, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 224)
      - Sloss, John H. (21), 1967-1970 (Box 37, Folder 225)
      - Stern, Harold S. (1), 1962 (Box 37, Folder 226)
      - Terris, Milton (3), 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 226)
      - Van Goor, Robert E. (11), 1961 (Box 37, Folder 227)
      - Vayda, Eugene (25), 1963-1968 (Box 37, Folder 228)
      - Webster, Jack (4), 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 229)
      - Willard, Harold N. (3), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 230)
      - Williams, Robert F. (3), 1962, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 230)
      - Wilson, Glenn (37), 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 231)
      - Wilson, Glenn (42), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 232)
      - Wilson, Glenn (50), 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 233)
      - Wilson, Glenn (29), 1966 (Box 38, Folder 234)
      - Wilson, Glenn (8), 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 235)
      - Yedidia, Avram (16), 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 236-237)
      - Yedidia, Avram (21), 1964-1967 (Box 38, Folder 238)
    - "Preliminary Report on Considerations in Planning a Community Health Program in Cleveland, Ohio" by the United States Public Health Service, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 239)
    - outline and summary of "Preliminary Report", 1961 (Box 38, Folder 240)
    - memoranda and notes re: planning and development of CHF, 1961-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 241)
    - minutes of meetings of CHF directors, 1963-1967 (Box 39, Folder 242-243)
    - proposed by-laws of CHF, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 244)
    - equipment, space, and supply requirements, 1962, undated (Box 39, Folder 245)
    - CHF benefit contracts, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 246)
    - CHF medical service agreements, 1964-1966 (Box 39, Folder 247)
    - projected budgets, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 248)
    - CHF audit, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 249)
    - misc. financial statements, 1964-1967, undated (Box 39, Folder 250)
    - articles of incorporation and code of regulations for Community Health Hospital, undated (Box 39, Folder 251)
    - public relations campaign plans for Community Health Foundation Hospital, undated (Box 39, Folder 252)
    - outline and plans for history of CHF, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 253)
    - "Pattern for a Medical Care Program" by A. Yedidia (chapters 1-7), 1964 (Box 40, Folder 254)
    - "Pattern for a Medical Care Program" by A. Yedidia (chapters 9-10), 1964 (Box 40, Folder 255)
    - "Pattern for a Medical Care Program", by A. Yedidia (chapters 1-6, 9) (Box 40, Folder 256)
    - CHF brochures (Box 40, Folder 257-259)
    - enrollment and membership information, undated (Box 40, Folder 260)
    - magazine articles and newspaper clippings on CHF (Box 40, Folder 261)
    - "Changing Patterns of Medical Care" by E. Vayda, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 262)
    - "Community Health Foundation" (report on CHF's history, aims, and financial status), 1965? (Box 40, Folder 263)
    - "The Community Health Foundation as a Demonstration in Comprehensive Health Care Planning" (no author listed), undated (Box 40, Folder 264)
    - "Community Health Foundation: Its Beginnings; Position Today; Plans for Tomorrow" (no author listed), 1967 (Box 40, Folder 265)
    - "Differential Patterns of Prenatal Care in a Prepaid Group Practice Medical Care Plan" by T. J. Comerford, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 266)
    - "Subscriber Response to Community Health Foundation" by M. Shakespeare, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 267)
    - misc. articles re: CHF (Box 40, Folder 268)
    - misc. (Box 40, Folder 269)
  - Community Health Foundation, Cleveland, Family Health Maintenance Project
    - memoranda, minutes, and other papers re: family health maintenance project, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 270)
    - memoranda, minutes, and other papers re: family health maintenance project, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 271)
    - memoranda, minutes, and other papers re: family health maintenance project, 1965-1968, undated (Box 41, Folder 272)
    - information on Community Health Services Project Grants (Box 41, Folder 273)
    - application for CHS project grant (early drafts), 1962 (Box 41, Folder 274)
    - application for CHS project grant: "Demonstration of Health Maintenance Services in a Prepaid Group Health Center Program", 1963 (Box 41, Folder 275)
    - revised project plan for "Demonstration of Health Services…", 1963 (Box 41, Folder 276)
    - planning requirements for CHS project grant, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 277)
    - progress report on CHS project grant, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 278)
    - application for CHS project grant, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 279-282)
    - request for continuation of CHS project grant, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 283-284)
    - application for supplement to CHS project grant, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 285)
    - misc. papers re: renewal of CHS project grant (Box 42, Folder 286)
    - description and objectives of family health maintenance project, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 287)
    - forms, questionnaires, etc. re: family health nurse (Box 42, Folder 288)
    - sample patient folders (Box 42, Folder 289)
    - forms and tables (Box 42, Folder 290)
    - application for grant: "Prevention of Coronary Heart Disease", 1965 (Box 42, Folder 291)
    - papers re: consultation and travel expenses, 1963-1969 (Box 42, Folder 292)
  - American Public Health Association, Guide to Medical Care
    - "Medical Care and the Health of the Nation" (proposed APHA policy statement), early drafts, 1961-1963 July (Box 43, Folder 293)
    - "Medical Care and the Health of the Nation" (proposed APHA policy statement), 1963 August-September (Box 43, Folder 294)
    - "An Introduction to Concepts and Principles of Medical Care Administration" (proposed APHA policy statement), 1964 (Box 43, Folder 295-296)
    - "A Guide to Medical Care Administration: Concepts and Principles" (report of the Program Area Committee on Medical Care Administration), 1965 (Box 43, Folder 297)
    - "A Guide to Medical Care Administration: Medical Care Appraisal-Quality and Utilization," pp. 1-140 (report by A. Donabedian for the Program Area Committee), 1968 (Box 43, Folder 298)
    - "A Guide to Medical Care Administration: Medical Care Appraisal-Quality and Utilization," pp. 141-321 (report by A. Donabedian for the Program Area Committee), 1968 (Box 43, Folder 299)
    - misc. (Box 43, Folder 300)
  - Yale Medical School and Hospital/Hill Neighborhood Corporation
    - "Report of First Year's Activities Academic Year 1962-1963" by E. R. Weinerman (Box 44, Folder 301)
    - "Report of Second Year's Activities Academic Year 1963-1964" by E. R. Weinerman (Box 44, Folder 302)
    - "Report of Third Year's Activities Academic Year 1964-1965" by E. R. Weinerman (Box 44, Folder 303)
    - "Report of Fourth Year's Activities of Academic Year 1965-1966" by E. R. Weinerman (Box 44, Folder 304)
    - "Report of Fifth Year's Activities Academic Year 1966-1967" by E. R. Weinerman (Box 44, Folder 305)
    - "Annual Report" of Office of Ambulatory Services, 1964-1966 (Box 44, Folder 306-308)
    - background material for 1963 conference on ambulatory services (Box 44, Folder 309)
    - background material for conference on ambulatory services, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 310)
    - background material for conference on ambulatory services, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 311)
    - background material for conference on ambulatory services, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 312)
    - background material for 1967 conference on ambulatory services (Box 44, Folder 313)
    - background material for 1968 conference on ambulatory services (Box 44, Folder 314)
    - applications and notes re: joint Yale-Montefiore Hospital residency program, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 315)
    - memoranda re: ambulatory services, 1962-1964, 1965, 1968, undated (Box 44, Folder 316)
    - memoranda re: Carnegie Corporation support of community health programs, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 317)
    - memoranda re: clinic teaching assigments, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 318)
    - memoranda and notes re: Connecticut Yugoslavia comparative study on regionalization, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 319)
    - memoranda re: leaves of absence, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 320)
    - memoranda re: medical school and community, 1967-1970 (Box 44, Folder 321)
    - memoranda and notes re: National Center for Health Services Research and Development, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 322)
    - memoranda re: public health department, 1964-1965, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 323)
    - memoranda and papers re: research activities and grants, 1963-1969 (Box 45, Folder 324)
    - memoranda re: Weinerman's appointment (Box 45, Folder 325)
    - notes for class lectures, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 326)
    - reports on summer clerkships at Thayer Hospital, 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 327)
    - "Methodology of Records and Statistics for Out-Patient Clinic Services" by E. R. Weinerman, L. H. Day, M. H. Brenner, and H. A. Paris, 1965/1966 (Box 45, Folder 328)
    - admitting procedure manual for Grace-New Haven Community Hospital (Box 45, Folder 329)
    - fee schedule for Grace-New Haven Community Hospital (Box 45, Folder 330)
    - procedure manuals for psychiatric clinic of Grace-New Haven Community Hospital (Box 45, Folder 331)
    - nursing reports from ambulatory service clinics, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 332)
    - nursing manual for the Winchester Chest Clinic (Box 45, Folder 333)
    - "The Role of the Nurse in Ambulatory Services" by C. E. Falls, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 334)
    - misc. (Box 45, Folder 335)
    - application for project grant: "Comprehensive Family Health Services" (proposed by the Hill Neighborhood Corporation), 1969 May-November (Box 46, Folder 336-338)
    - model neighborhoods application (Box 46, Folder 339)
    - statement of Yale's involvement in Hill Health Center, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 340)
  - Social Medicine in Eastern Europe
    - Correspondence:
      - The Commonwealth Fund (25), 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 341)
      - The Harvard University Press (58), 1968-1969, undated (Box 47, Folder 342)
      - Social Medicine in Eastern Europe by E. R. Weinerman (pp. 1-112), 1967 (Box 47, Folder 343)
      - Social Medicine in Eastern Europe by E. R. Weinerman (pp. 113-273), 1967 (Box 47, Folder 344)
      - Social Medicine in Eastern Europe draft for printer (pp. 1-149) (Box 47, Folder 345)
      - Social Medicine in Eastern Europe draft for printer (pp. 150-272) (Box 47, Folder 346)
      - notices and reviews of Social Medicine in Eastern Europe (Box 47, Folder 347)
      - letters and papers re: travel arrangements (Box 47, Folder 348)
      - misc. (Box 47, Folder 349)
  - Miscellaneous Consultation
    - miscellaneous consultations (Box 47, Folder 350)
  - Background Material for Health Care Survey of Israel, New Zealand, and Japan
    - background material on Australian health services pamphlets, etc.) (Box 47A, Folder 351)
    - background material on Australian health services (Box 47A, Folder 352)
    - background material on New Zealand health services (Box 47A, Folder 353-354)
    - background material on Israeli health services (Box 47A, Folder 355-359)
    - background material on Japanese health services (Box 47A, Folder 360)
- Medical, Political, and Social Activities and Organizations, Series III; 3.75 linear feet (9 boxes)